Cabbage
So many!
Love Fair
The Nikujaga of Love
Nikujaga- meat and potato stew​
For a home date or special occasion
You did it, Maruyama-kun!
Yes.
But we all didn't have to come here to see.
If our project goes through, we come and see it in action.
This is the custom of our department.
Listen to this adult.
I am an adult.
Senpai, allow me to thank you once again.
Thank?
It is thanks to you that this project became successful.
No, no I didn't do anything.
I am grateful to you.
Advising me on call,
and accompanying me
for researches even on your days off.
What's going on?
You two seem pretty close.
We are close.
If I had a younger brother, it would be like this.
But I don't want you to be my older sister.
What do you mean?
Just what I said.
But this is really cool.
Fancy Nikujaga for a home date.
And the target is also huge.
I mean there's no one in this world who doesn't fall in love.
Right?
Kodama, you too.
Don't be just all about work,
think about the love side too.
This kind of experience can be
utilized in product development
and also help people grow.
If this project is a hit,
please make it a series!
That's too much!
I'll pick it up.
I'm sorry.
Did it get spoiled?
In that case, I'll buy it.
No.
We'll wash it again
and use it in the deli section if it can't be used here.
I'm sorry.
Is YR Harukaze this cabbage's name?
Yes.
So it is, right?
Earlier while looking at the vegetable section
I found YR Harukaze written on
a cabbage curious.
If it has a name, I want to use it properly.
I don't want to be collectively called as a human either.
By any chance,
is the one who arranges the vegetables here
you, Takahashi-san?
Well, yes.
I like the way they are arranged!
Using a different-colored vegetable
to separate similar-colored ones.
Thank you.
The one who wrote these thorough display boards
is also you, Takahashi-san?
Yes.
Thought so!
Do you maybe like cabbages?
The explanation for it was more detailed than the rest and...
Excuse me but...
You people are from the headquarters right?
Yes.
How do you know my name?
Because it's there.
Fruits
& Vegetables
TAKAHASHI
By the way, I am Kodama Sakuko from Sales Planning Department.
Not Saki, it's Sakuko.
Sakuko-san.
What's up with that eye contact!
Falling in love right in front of the 'Love Nikujaga'?
No I am just Takahashi-san's...
Takahashi-san's...
fan of how he arranges vegetables.
Also,
I believe they exist.
People who don't fall in love.
~ Kaizen Subs ~
(@KaizenSubs)
Translation - @GK170502
Timing - @CHI159SHORI & @ofcodeskeys
~ Kaizen Subs ~
(@KaizenSubs)
Translation - @GK170502
Timing - @CHI159SHORI & @ofcodeskeys
~ Kaizen Subs ~
(@KaizenSubs)
Translation - @GK170502
Timing - @CHI159SHORI & @ofcodeskeys
~ Kaizen Subs ~
(@KaizenSubs)
Translation - @GK170502
Timing - @CHI159SHORI & @ofcodeskeys
~ Kaizen Subs ~
(@KaizenSubs)
Translation - @GK170502
Timing - @CHI159SHORI & @ofcodeskeys
~ Kaizen Subs ~
(@KaizenSubs)
Translation - @GK170502
Timing - @CHI159SHORI & @ofcodeskeys
I'm sorry, I went too far I guess.
I have preparation to do for the opening.
See you.
Thanks for your hard work.
Is anything wrong?
You called that greengrocer by his name suddenly.
Takahashi-san? Is it so?
He was not wearing any wedding ring you know?
So what?
Please don't get close to everyone you see.
Do you not think about how I would feel?
How you would feel?
I don't want to be your younger brother or junior anymore.
You already know how I feel right?
What are you talking about?
I mean...
weren't we looking good together?
Almost like lovers!
I mean you also like me, right?
No...
I am sorry.
Was that my fault?
Not at all.
It was just your junior who misunderstood it.
Leave him alone.
I just wanted to cheer on a junior who was working hard.
All we talked about was work.
There are people who try to connect everything with love.
I don't even want to be connected.
I have been saying that I just want to focus on work for now.
You're after all not good with
romantic relationships.
You want to say that I suck at it again?
Chizuru you're so mean!
Do you remember it?
During high school, we went to a cake buffet.
And when the love talks started...
Seems like Kanae and Fumiya are dating.
Really? Finally!
I always thought they would definitely date!
...feels like that, right?
I want to fall in love~
Do you both not have anyone you like?
You didn't join the conversation,
ate five plates of cake and fell ill.
Even with the boyfriend you got along well with,
in the end, you two broke up quickly.
You really remember such things clearly.
You just don't seem to have any luck in love.
I wonder why.
Maybe it's just my fault.
No it's not.
You're the best.
Come on, eat up.
My treat.
Is it mixing?
It is.
I am sure you'll meet someone perfect for you someday.
I wonder about that.
Love isn't something you should be forcing yourself to do.
Lately, I've been thinking I'm done with love and all that.
Right! We've had enough of all that.
It's my freewill whether
to love or not.
It is right?
I like you Chizuru~
You're the best and strongest.
You know,
it's a different topic but
my house's contract has to be renewed soon.
So someone I can share my room with...
Count me in!
That was quick!
Are you being serious?
Yes I am!
Onee-chan!
She'll wake up.
Sorry!
You're going to move out?
Without even discussing with us.
We decided it today.
From tomorrow we'll go looking for an apartment
and settle where we find a good one.
Isn't that all so quick?
Right?
Isn't it okay?
Let her do what she wants.
That way I can use her room whenever I come here.
Isn't it okay?
See, once you leave your parents' house and then come back
you'll miss your chance to marry.
Mom, you also said so, right?
That Sakuko needs to give birth to a male grandchild soon.
Minori!
Chizuru-san can introduce you to someone.
Well, well, well, it doesn't really matter.
It's this late already?
I'll go home then.
Maya-chan is still sleeping,
how about staying here tonight?
I'll carry her on my back.
You can't do that.
Papa, send her off.
Sakuko, I'm sorry but could you please clean up?
Okay~
Why did you talk about that with your sister?
About what?
We shouldn't pressurize her.
She might look fine but
we're definitely hurrying her to get married.
You always have said that it's better to give birth
at an early age, haven't you?
That is...
I mean she's old enough.
She must be enjoying her work.
But it's surprising.
I thought you didn't want to leave your parents' place.
I love my family.
When we're all together, we're noisy.
It's fun and relaxing.
But my sister also visits us.
'When are you going to marry?'
'Your younger sister beat you to it'
When they say things like that,
I feel pressured.
Lately I've been feeling like there's no place for me at home.
But living alone is...
I would be scared of always being alone.
What do you mean scared?
Anyway, if I can live together with you,
that would be our place.
It would be best if that can become our castle.
Our castle?
It's a little small for a castle though.
It is.
But...
Feels good.
Rather, it's the best!
It's dangerous!
We found it.
Without anything bothersome like love or romance.
Our own castle.
A dream life
for two.
Are you moving out?
You...
Living together?
When did you get a boyfriend?
I am going to be roommates with a friend from high school.
That friend is a woman?
Yes.
Then some advice from me.
Don't be so fired up to get the furniture.
Because that'll have a deadline.
That is until either of you get a boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Work over love character continues?
Guess so.
There you again.
Kodama.
Yes?
Can you take over Maruyama's project from today?
He suddenly said he wanted to change his department.
And also that he would take some time off from work.
Kodama, you were close with him, right?
Ask him the reason.
Counting on you.
You've been working hard.
Thanks for your hard work too.
Is it my fault?
What's wrong?
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
Why are you zoning out?
Did something happen?
Not really.
This weekend, I'm going to
put a crib in your room.
Is it okay?
Minori's room has become Papa's study.
How's the packing? Almost done?
Don't depend everything on Chizuru-chan.
Do your work on your own.
I know that!
Here it is!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Almost there!
Got it! Waiting in front of the cafe.
Our apartment is finalized
Yes! Looking forward to
living in our castle!
Can we meet now?
Look at this, isn't it cute?
Thought about decorating our room with it.
Sorry.
I got back together with my ex-boyfriend.
And he asked me to live together with him.
In that apartment?
No.
In his house itself.
Sorry, this is sudden.
I wanted to meet and apologize directly.
I should be congratulating you, right?
Sorry! I couldn't say it properly.
I just got a little carried away.
I said I am sorry!
But I can't help it because I love him!
There are these uncontrollable things that
come out of nowhere!
I am human!
Then I am going.
Sakuko.
I hope you also...
meet your fated partner soon.
Is it my fault?
What does fated partner mean?
A dating site to meet your
fated partner 'andUwithU'
What should you do in order to
meet your fated partner?
Learn a secret technique.
Free Fortune telling-
Who is your fated partner?
Where and when will you meet?
What does fated
partner mean?
Can't fall in love, don't understand
Can't fall in love, don't understand, strange
The reason why young people
nowadays don't fall in love
Is it strange to not want to get
married? Merits of not marrying.
Use this dating app 'Marient'
if you don't want to fall in love.
Change your loveless
lifestyle with these 3 steps
and meet your fated partner.
Women are in danger
if they don't fall in love..?
'Love is troublesome, but I want to get
married.' Marriage site 'Marry Meet'
is for such people.
Regardless of your knowledge
about aroaces, it's weirder to
say that to not fall in love is weird.
Regardless of your knowledge
about aroaces, it's weirder to
say that to not fall in love is weird.
''AroDiary of Haneiro Cabbage''?
Regardless of your knowledge about aroaces,
What I think about love
it's weird to say that to not fall in love is weird.
Aroace?
Aro Ace
About Aromantic/Asexuals:
Romantic and Sexual Orientation
Not having either romantic or
sexual feelings: Aromantic Asexual
About Aromantic/Asexuals:
Romantic and Sexual Orientation
What does asexual mean?
What does aromantic mean?
Aromantic-Asexuals
"Asexual is a form of sexual orientation.
Used to refer to people who are not sexually attracted to others.''
Asexual
Sexual Orientation
People who are not sexually attracted to others
Aromantic
"Aromantic is one of the romantic orientations.
Romantic Orientation
Used to refer to people who do not have romantic feelings for others.''
people who who do not have romantic feelings for others
I cut some pear.
''They say, 'If you're not married at that age,
people will think there's some problem.'
That thought process is the most problematic.
The cabbage rolls I made yesterday were excellent, so that's good.''
'''You won't meet anyone if you just keep waiting.'
I'm not waiting for anyone, I'm rather avoiding.''
Kodama-san, please take care of this.
Okay.
''Someone at work suggested me to go on a blind date.''
When I turned them down, they said,
'That's a shame, you're not in a position to be choosy.'
I can tell right away that they're
looking down on people by that comment.
"Why do people make so much fun of those who don't fall in love?''
I see.
So people have been making fun of me?
''People say- You like being alone, don't you?
This troubles me because it's not true.''
Takahashi-san, when you're done there, please come here also.
Okay.
Takahashi-san.
Kodama...
Sakuko-san?
You've been working hard.
You too.
That.
Curry Udon: Udon soup and Japanese curry
It's curry udon.
It attacked you on the day you're wearing a white shirt.
It attacked too much.
What brings you here today?
I took over a junior colleague's job.
And am waiting for my superior.
That simplistic superior?
If a man and woman are close to each other,
he will immediately assume that they are in love.
He's not a bad guy.
But you seemed tired to me.
Sorry.
I said something out of line.
Curry Udon
What is it?
Are you Haneiro Cabbage-san?
Excuse me!
I...
wanted to ask you about a lot of things.
I also might be that aro...
You shouldn't...
talk about...
that stuff in such a loud voice.
So you're Haneiro Cabbage-san!
I am so happy!
I can relate to everything that's
written in your blog.
If possible I want to...
Uhm...
What time does your job end?
Does Haneiro (羽色) Cabbage have any meaning?
My name is written as hane (羽) and read as Satoru.
That's a lovely name!
We both have unusual names.
Where should we talk?
The cafe near the station, a family restaurant...
There is the chance of bumping into someone familiar...
Anywhere is fine!
It will be problematic for me.
If you don't like it, please tell me...
My home is very close by...
Let's go there!
Right from here.
Rig- There!
Left from there.
Okay.
Here it is.
Let's go somewhere else.
No...
It's a lovely house.
Then...
Things are a little scattered around.
Sorry for intruding.
It's lovely after all.
Thank you.
I'll pour some tea.
It's Takahashi-san's castle~
What?
I have a friend called Chizuru.
Yes?
My friendships don't last too long but
Chizuru is different.
Is it okay if I talk about myself a little?
Please go ahead.
Actually I was going to
be her roommate and live together with her.
But she began dating her ex-boyfriend again
and we canceled living together.
That time...
she said ''I hope you meet your fated partner soon.''
That really pricked me.
And so I looked up some stuff on the Net and...
Found my blog.
And your identity.
I am not sure yet.
But I completely relate to it.
Until then...
I am stupid but...
I thought that
I was useless and hopeless.
It's not like that.
But people have always told me that
''You'll understand once you start to date.''
''You'll feel it when you like someone.''
''You'll learn it when you grow up.''
Everyone says that but...
It never goes well.
I thought I was lacking something as a human.
That's why...
The word Aromantic Asexual,
no, your words have saved me.
To be honest, I am not prepared yet.
Prepared?
To not fall in love probably means
that I'll have to live on my own.
It'll be good if I am able to live with my parents
but to not be able to follow through their hopes,
and to not be understood is hard.
The place where I belong,
I have to build my own castle.
But...
But?
I don't
like being alone.
And when I think that
from now and forever, I'll be alone,
I feel very lonely.
Sorry, I am being selfish.
It can't be helped.
I don't think it's like that.
No matter what someone's sexuality might be,
to want to be with someone and to feel lonely alone
is not being selfish.
Then what should I do?
I don't know.
Half a year ago,
I lost my grandmother who raised me.
I was mentally prepared
for this separation but...
I still feel lonely.
It must be.
I am sorry.
Having you listen to my gloomy story.
I still...
don't know what to do.
But...
I have no intentions to call this feeling selfish.
Ah yes, the snacks someone gave me...
Uhm...
Yes?
Would you become a family with me?
What?
Excluding all romantic feelings,
would you become a family with me?
Are you...
making fun of me?
I was wondering if we could become a family without any romantic feelings.
New boyfriend?
Where are you living right now?
Sorry.
It's okay.
This means that I have to pretend to be your lover?